

CONTACT



059-240-4201



ayieric7@gmail.com



GA-441-7501, Nungua



grinbox.com

SKILLS

MS Word. MS Excel

Web Development



Strategic Planning

Technical Writing



Business Communication



LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - - -

HOBBIES









Eric Kodzo Ayi

Seasoned Technical Support Officer with 3 years of comprehensive experience in Software development. Methodical and meticulous professional polished in identifying technical issues and solving them. Excellent quantitative and critical thinking abilities paired with advanced knowledge of SQL and JAVASCRIPT.

WORK HISTORY

Business Analyst, IT Officer, Tulip Groupe

2020-2022

- Analyses potential businesses in Ghana regarding real estate, tourism and agriculture
- Designed and regularly updates the company's real estate brochure.
- Performs periodic maintenance on the company's website and online workspace (Google Drive)
- Manages the company's database.

MRW Operator, NIA, Ghana

2018-2020

- Captured biometric data (fingerprints, iris & portrait) of potential citizens
- Entered applicants' biographic data including verification of relevant documents, and scanning them
- Cross-examined filled application forms for any possible errors that may occur during applicants' interview
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.

Technical Support Engineer (NSS), CSIR-IIR 2016-2017

- Created plans and communicated deadlines to ensure projects were completed on time.
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties.
- Oversaw daily operations to ensure high levels of productivity.
- Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Chemical Engineering

2012-2016

University of Science and Technology

Certificate

2008-2012

Keta Senior High Technical School

CERTIFICATIONS

Full-Stack Engineer Career Path	2022
Learn jQuery course	2021
Learn Sass course	2021
Learn Vue.is course	2021